do you understand what an anticlimax Yes you were
world champion 47 seconds ago it was
clear No damn Yes I BL so damn Lack
I had BL so fucking varnish Yes exactly off
all the days you could beat my record take
another day at least What What is there
for branches then summer sports d in the Olympics
badminton Yes basketball table tennis boxing
wrestling archery cycling football
athletics fencing golf gymnastics
handball, judo, artistic swimming, field hockey
modern pentathlon equestrian sport Rowing rugby
sailing diving swimming shooting ta kwando
tennis triathlon weightlifting water polo
and volleyball I know which one I had
taken Who should say first or say you
I had run fencing Why it It is